<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anjula&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://anjulalk.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anjula&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Anjula Karunarathne.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anjulalk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Google Summer of Code 2020 Project with Joplin Notebook</title>
      <link>https://anjulalk.github.io/my-google-summer-of-code-2020-project-with-joplin-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjulalk.github.io/my-google-summer-of-code-2020-project-with-joplin-notebook/</guid>
      <description>Joplin desktop application supports keyboard shortcuts to a certain degree. However, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t an option for users to configure keyboard shortcuts according to their preferences. My project was to implement a keyboard shortcut editor along with the necessary integration.
The project consisted of two parts:
 Back-end service for handling all keymapping-related functionality Keyboard shortcut editor with the necessary functionality to alter the keymap  Progress The project was implemented in two pull requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survive Android Studio with 4GB of Memory</title>
      <link>https://anjulalk.github.io/survive-android-studio-with-4gb-of-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjulalk.github.io/survive-android-studio-with-4gb-of-memory/</guid>
      <description>Even though it says in Android Studio download page that the minimum required memory is 4GB, you will feel the struggle when you run it in a machine with less than 8GB of memory.
Fortunately, there are a few tweaks you can use to make it somewhat bearable. Some of these might be not much effective, but trust me; you need every bit of performance you can get.
Switch to a lightweight Linux distribution Using a lightweight Linux distribution will make it much easier than running Android Studio with that memory hog called Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://anjulalk.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anjulalk.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects 💻 This page is coming, soon.
Find my projects on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
